greenchildmagazine.com 2017-11-21

# Privacy Policy

**Fresh Green Media, LLC Privacy Policy**  
Updated on January 25, 2017

At Fresh Green Media, LLC (parent company of Green Child Magazine), your privacy is important to us. This privacy policy applies to all websites, apps, services and publications provided by Fresh Green Media, LLC (FGM, LLC).

We value our relationship with you and provide this policy to better protect your privacy and explain how your information is used by FGM, LLC.

If you ever have any questions about our privacy policy, magazine, website or parent company FGM, LLC please feel free to contact us at info@freshgreenmediallc.com or by post at the address below:

Fresh Green Media, LLC  
P.O. Box 14423  
Gainesville, FL 32607

 **What information do we collect?**

We collect information from you when you register on our site, subscribe to our newsletter, respond to a survey or fill out a form.

When registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name, e-mail address or mailing address. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.

 **What do we use your information for?**

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:

  * To personalize your experience (Your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs.)
  * To improve our website (We continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you.)
  * To improve customer service (Your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs.)
  * To process transactions – such as giveaways (Your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested.)
  * To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature
  * To send periodic emails (The email address you provide for order processing, may be used to send you information and updates pertaining to your order, in addition to receiving occasional company news, updates, related product or service information, etc.)
  * Note: If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email.

 **Do we use cookies?**

Yes – Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information.

We use cookies to understand and save your preferences for future visits and compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future. We may contract with third-party service providers to assist us in better understanding our site visitors. These service providers are not permitted to use the information collected on our behalf except to help us conduct and improve our business.

 **Do we disclose any information to outside parties?**

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

 **Third party links**

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

 **Affiliate Disclosure**

In compliance with the FTC guidelines, please assume the following about all links, posts, photos and other material on this website:

Any/all of the links on this website are affiliate links of which Fresh Green Media, LLC receives a small commission from sales of certain items, but the price is the same for you.

Green Child Magazine is a participant in the Amazon Services LLC Associates Program, an affiliate advertising program designed to provide a means for sites to earn advertising fees by linking to products we feel our readers may find helpful on [Amazon.com](http://amzn.to/2jqLXV4).

For instance, if you click on a link on this website for an [Instant Pot](http://amzn.to/2kutsRu), [glass storage cubes](http://amzn.to/2jghber), [baby swing](http://amzn.to/2j6ahgq), or any other item we link to from Amazon, we will receive a small commission (the average is around $1.00 to $1.42 per item).

 **Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance**

We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.

 **Your Consent**

By using our site, you consent to our websites privacy policy.

 **Changes to our Privacy Policy**

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page.

  * About
  * Latest Posts

### [Green Child Magazine](http://www.greenchildmagazine.com/)

Since 2010, Green Child has published a digital magazine devoted to natural parenting and conscious living. Hailed as “good for a green mama’s soul,” Green Child has grown into a resource valued by parents who care about bringing simplicity, compassion, social responsibility, and instinctual intelligence back to parenting.

#### Latest posts by Green Child Magazine ([see all](http://www.greenchildmagazine.com/author/green-child-magazine/))
